Guide to the Bound for Glory records, 1969-2015.
Bound for Glory records, 1969-2015.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Bound for Glory records 1969-2015.
35-9-4277
Shapiro, Phillip Donald
20
Audioreels
125
gigabytes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Audio recordings of the radio shows featuring a wide range of folk performers. Reels include inserts with handwritten notes by Shapiro about the performances and a list of the songs played. The notes and lists may have spelling errors and song titles may have been generated from how the song sounded not the actual title. Some notes also include markings to indicate songs that were particularly notable.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Bound for Glory is North America's longest running live folk concert radio broadcast. The show is broadcast live on WVBR 93.5 FM from Anabel Taylor Hall on the Cornell University campus Sunday nights. While the name of the room where the show is broadcast has changed over the years, the Commons Coffeehouse, Cul de Snack, the Cafe at Anabel Taylor, Alternatives Library, the space itself in Anabel Taylor has remained constant. Phil Shapiro made his first Ithaca broadcast of the show in September 1967 on the WVBR radio station. Bound for Glory presents folk music of all types and has run for over 1,500 concerts.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Materials relating to the history of the Bound for Glory folk music show. Audio recordings of the Bound for Glory radio shows featuring a wide range of folk performers. Reels include inserts with handwritten notes by Shapiro about the performances and a list of the songs played. The notes and lists may have spelling errors and song titles may have been generated from how the song sounded not the actual title. Some notes also include markings to indicate songs that were particularly notable.
Also digital recordings created by Doug Steinfeld off tapes collected by himself, Sari Goldbaum, and Janet Elis. These items are identified as part of the Doug Steinfeld collection.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Shapiro, Phillip Donald; WVBR (Radio Station: Cornell University)
Subjects:
Folk music; Folk songs; Radio broadcasting.
Form and Genre Terms:
tape reels
INFORMATION FOR USERS
A portion of these recordings come from the collection of Doug Steinfeld. These tapes were digitized by Steinfeld who remains in possession of the physical tapes. Some of these recordings have a break from the initial recording when the tape was flipped over during set two of the performance. The Steinfeld collection also contains a set of Encore tapes. These tapes contain encores for shows that were not necessarily included on the on air broadcast or on the show tape.
RELATED MATERIALS
See also WVBR records, #35-9-1739. http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA01739.
The Bound for Glory Documentary is available online here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iF3N2xA5RB8
CONTAINER LIST
- Bound for Glory The Documentary by Brad Kolodner (digital), 2012
  Short documentary by Brad Kolodner and Aya Hoffman when they were Ithaca College seniors. "This is a story about the passion and love one man has for folk music and the sacrifices he's made to keep this folk treasure alive."
- Bound for Glory 1500th Show Phil Shapiro Tribute Book (digital), 2015
  CD-2668 a digital copy of the book.
- Clint Swank, September 28, 1969; tr-15957 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 14
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 8
  Track: Side 1 Track 1
  Track list: Arrival; I Don't Amount to Much Without You; Mary, Martha and John; August Circumstances; Empty Space; While the Getting is Good; Volcanos; Twelve Turns to Midnight; Black; Here I Am Again; Peggy [unreadable]; Halfway Up the Stairs
- Tony Barnard and John Roberts, October 5, 1969; tr-15957 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 15
  Track: Side 2 Track 1
  Track list:
- Howie Bursen and Bret Littlehales, October 12, 1969; tr-15957 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 16
  Track: Side 1 Track 2
- Jon Sabin, October 19, 1969; tr-15957 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 17
  Track: Side 2 Track 2
- Bill Destler and Doug Wright, October 26, 1969; tr-15958 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 18
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 9
- Ken Perlman, November 2, 1969; tr-15958 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 19
- Chris Bigelow, November 9, 1969; tr-15958 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 20
- Gary Weiner, Pat Slaney, Walt Koken with Eddy Tuleja, Hugh Cregg and Marty Lebenson, November 16, 1969; tr-15958 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 21
- John Gréven, David Levine and Larry Eaton, November 23, 1969; tr-15959 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 22
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 10
- Phil Shapiro, December 7, 1969; tr-15959 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 23
- Meg Garvey and John Simson with Dennis Wesler, December 14, 1969; tr-15959 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 24
- John Hostetter, Alan Sorvall, Dave Turner, February 1, 1970; tr-15959 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 25
- Jon Sabin, February 8, 1970; tr-15960 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 26
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 11
- Eric Mintz and Bill Destler, February 15, 1970; tr-15960 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 27
- Charisse duBorgel, February 22, 1970; tr-15960 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 28
- Russ Barenberg, Bret Littlehales, John Ellis and Howie Bursen, March 1, 1970; tr-15960 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 29
- Jeff Comaner, March 8, 1970; tr-15961 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 30
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 12
- Clint Swank, March 15, 1970; tr-15961 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 31
- Paul Geremia, March 22, 1970; tr-15961 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 32
- Chris Bigelow, April 12, 1970; tr-15961 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 33
- Ken Perlman, April 19, 1970; tr-15962 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 34
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 13
- Dana Prisant, Harry Gordon, Dave Kent, April 26, 1970; tr-15962 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 35
- Atley and Lydia, May 3, 1970; tr-15962 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 36
- Charlie Starr, May 10, 1970; tr-15962 (Box 1)
- Folk Festival with John Roberts and Tony Barrand, Helen Schneyer, Ricky Schneyer, Cliff Haslam, Martin Grosswendt, Estelle Wade, Barbara Carns with Russ Berenberg and Bret Littlehales, Nick Appolonio, Janet Kelley, Margaret MacArthur, May 17, 1970; tr-15963 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 37
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 14
  Track: Side 1 and Side 2
- Folk Festival with John Roberts and Tony Barrand, Helen Schneyer, Ricky Schneyer, Cliff Haslam, Martin Grosswendt, Estelle Wade, Barbara Carns with Russ Berenberg and Bret Littlehales, Nick Appolonio, Janet Kelley, Margaret MacArthur, May 17, 1970; tr-15964 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 38
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 15
  Track: Side 1
- Howie Bursen, May 24, 1970; tr-15965 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 39
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 16
- John Gréven, June 28, 1970; tr-15965 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 40
- Charisse duBorgel, July 5, 1970; tr-15965 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 41
- Bill Destler, July 12, 1970; tr-15965 (Box 1)
- John Roberts and Tony Barrand with Colett Curry and Ricki Schneyer, July 19, 1970; tr-15966 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 42
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 17
- John Roberts and Tony Barrand with Colett Curry and Ricki Schneyer, July 19, 1970; tr-15966 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 43
- Allen Sorval, Russ Barenberg, Gary Scheufler with Deena Zalkind and Susan Longacre, July 26, 1970; tr-15966 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 44
- Bill Vanaver, August 2, 1970; tr-15966 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 45
- Contraband Countryband (Peter Wernick, Joan Nondi Leonard, Russ Barenberg), August 9, 1970; tr-15966 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 46
- Clint Swank, September 13, 1970; tr-15967 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 47
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 18
- John Roberts, September 20, 1970; tr-15967 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 48
- Charisse duBorgel with Michele duBorgel, September 27, 1970; tr-15967 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 49
- Dave Kent, October 4, 1970; tr-15967 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 50
- John Miller, October 11, 1970; tr-15968 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 51
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 19
- Howie Bursen, October 18, 1970; tr-15968 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 52
- Bret Littlehales, October 25, 1970; tr-15968 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 53
- Meg Garvey, November 1, 1970; tr-15968 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 54
- John Roberts and Tony Barrand, November 8, 1970; tr-15969 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 55
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 20
- Barbara Carns, November 15, 1970; tr-15969 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 56
- Charlie Starr, November 22, 1970; tr-15969 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 57
- Ted Wurmbrand, November 29, 1970; tr-15969 (Box 1)
- Bill Destler and Paul Geremia with Jack McGann, December 6, 1970; tr-15970 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 58
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 21
- Bill Destler and Paul Geremia with Jack McGann, December 6, 1970; tr-15970 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 59
- Chris Bigelow, December 13, 1970; tr-15970 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 60
- Bill Destler, January 10, 1971; tr-15970 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 61
- Gayle Barr, January 17, 1971; tr-15970 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 62
- Clint Swank, January 31, 1971; tr-15971 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 63
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 22
- Russ Barenberg, John Miller and Susan Longacre, February 7, 1971; tr-15971 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 64
- Marathon with John Roberts and Tony Barrand, Grant Rogers, Dan Smith, Howie Bursen, Estelle Wade, Jerry Epstein, February 14, 1971; tr-15964 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 65
- Charisse duBorgel, February 21, 1971; tr-15971 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 66
- Doug Wright, February 28, 1971; tr-15971 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 67
- Ken Perlman, March 7, 1971; tr-15972 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 68
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 23
- Bill Vanaver, March 14, 1971; tr-15972 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 69
- Country Cookin' (Peter Wernick, Joan Nondi Leonard, Russ Barenberg, John Miller), March 21, 1971; tr-15972 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 70
- Old Salt, April 11, 1971; tr-15972 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 71
- John Miller, April 18, 1971; tr-15973 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 72
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 24
- Howie Bursen, April 25, 1971; tr-15973 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 73
- Dave Kent, May 2, 1971; tr-15973 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 74
- John Simson, May 9, 1971; tr-15973 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 75
- John Roberts and Tony Barrand, May 16, 1971; tr-15974 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 76
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 25
- Folk Festival with John Roberts and Tony Barrand, Nick Krukovsky, Bob Clayton, Martin Grosswendt, Jeff Warner, Johny Beggin and Seamus Walker, Ricki Schneyer, Janet Kelley, Peter Johnson, May 23, 1971; tr-15975 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 77
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 26
- Charlie Starr, June 27, 1971; tr-15974 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 78
- Bill Destler, July 4, 1971; tr-15974 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 79
- Gayle Barr, July 11, 1971; tr-15974 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 80
- Ann Redfoot, July 18, 1971; tr-15976 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 81
  Bound for Glory Tape #: 27
- Andy Cohen and Rat, July 25, 1971; tr-15976 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 82
- John Roberts and Tony Barrand, August 1, 1971; tr-15976 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 83
- Charlie Starr, September 5, 1971; tr-15976 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 84
- Peggy Haine, November 14, 1976; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 261
  Doug Steinfeld collection
- Peggy Haine, May 15, 1977; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 279
- Bill Staines, April 9, 1978; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 308
- Robin and Linda Williams, April 23, 1978; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 310
- Nick Seeger, February 11, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 336
- Bill Steele, February 18, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 337
- Stan Rogers, April 1, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 341
- Mark Rust, April 8, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 342
- Racquette River Rounders, April 15, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 343
- Robin and Linda Williams w/Peter Ostrushko, April 22, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 344
- Free Hollow, May 6, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 346
- Joyful Noise String Band w/Bob Wey, July 1, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 348
- Pierce Campbell and Dane Marion, July 8, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 349
- Bill Destler and Roger Sherman and Friends, July 15, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 350
- Alex Campbell, July 22, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 351?
- Bill Steele, July 29, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 352
- Howie Bursen with T.L. Osborne, Doug Knowles, John Bailey, September 2, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 353
- Knock Na Sheen, September 9, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 354
- Gary Meixner, September 16, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 355
- Jane Voss and Hoyle Osborn, September 23, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 356
- The Backwoods Band, September 30, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 357
- Cayuga Bluegrass Works, October 6, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 358
- Fiction Brothers, October 14, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 359
- Mark Rust, October 28, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 360
- Carolyn Odell, November 4, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 361
- Diamond Back Rattlers, November 11, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 362
- Mose Scarlet and Jim McLean, November 18, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 363
- Bill Steele, December 2, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 364
- Cranberry Lake, December 9, 1979; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 365
- Peggy Haine, Dane Marion, Brian Earle, Johnny Russo, January 20, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 366
- Nick Seeger, January 27, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 367
- Gary Meixner, February 3, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 368
- Henrie Family, February 17, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 370
- Howie Bursen and Friends, February 24, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 371
- Roger Sherman, March 9, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 373
- Papa John Kolstad, March 30, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 374
- Robin and Linda Williams, April 6, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 375
- Mark Rust, April 13, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 376
- Rustical Quality String Band, April 20, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 377
- Backwoods Band, April 27, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 378
- Bob White and Kevin Maul, May 4, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 379
- Paul Geremia (with Roy Bookbinder), May 11, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 379A?
- Press on Regardless Stringband, June 29, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 380
- Mitzi Collins and Skip Evans, July 6, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 381
- Bill Destler, July 13, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 382
- Joyful Noise String Band, July 20, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 383
- John McCutcheon, July 27, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 384
- Bill Staines, September 7, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 385
- Peggy Haine and the Lowdown Alligator Jass Band, September 21, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 387
- Bill Steele, September 28, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 388
- Desperado, October 5, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 389
- Gemini (Sandor and Lazlo Slomovits), October 19, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 390
- Papa John Kolstad, October 26, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 391?
- Scott Alarik, November 2, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 392
- Sally Rogers, November 9, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 393
- Cranberry Lake, November 16, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 394
- Wendy Grossman, November 23, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 395
- Priscilla Herdman, December 7, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 396
- Mark Rust, December 14, 1980; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 397
- Diamond Back Rattlers, February 8, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 398
- Lisa Null and Bill Shute, March 22, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 404
- Racquette River Rounders, April 12, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 405
- Robin and Linda Williams w/Jay Ungar and Lyndon Hardy, April 19, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 406
- Michael Green w/Cheryl Hurwitz, May 10, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 409
- Eric Thompson and Suzie Rothfield, May 17, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 410
- Polecat Bar Band w/Peter Bennett, July 12, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 412
- Bill Destler, July 19, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 413
- Joyful Noise String Band w/Bob Wey, July 26, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 414
- Wendy Grossman, August 2, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 415
- Claudio Buchwald and the Razor Lickers, August 9, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 416
- Carolyn O'Dell, September 13, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 418
- Spiritwood, September 20, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 419
- Scott Alarik, September 27, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 420
- Dady Brothers (John Dady, Joe Dady, Mike Pavone, Kevin Maul), October 4, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 421
- Geoff Bartley, October 11, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 422
- Papa John Kolstad, October 25, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 423
- Caryl P. Weiss, November 1, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 424
- Bristol Mountain Bluegrass, November 8, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 425
- Cranberry Lake, November 15, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 426
- Howie Bursen with Sally Rogers, John Bailey, Nick Krukovsky, December 6, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 428
- Peggy Haine and the Lowdown Alligator Jass Band, December 13, 1981; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 429
- Andy Wallace and Friends, October 17, 1982; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 456
- Bristol Mountain Bluegrass, October 24, 1982; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 457
- Peggy Haine and the Lowdown Alligator Jass Band, October 31, 1982; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 458?
- Scott Alarik, November 7, 1982; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 459
- Scott Alarik, November 7, 1982; tr-17858 (Box 2)
  Marie McRae collection
- Gary Meixner, November 14, 1982; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 460
- Sally Rogers, November 21, 1982; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 461
- Polecat Bar Band, February 27, 1983; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 469
- Michael Jerling w/Bob Warren, March 13, 1983; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 471
- Robin and Linda Williams, May 1, 1983; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 476
- Dady Brothers and Phil Shapiro, August 7, 1983; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 483
- Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen, October 21, 1984; tr-17861 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 524
- Rosalie Sorrels, May 4, 1986; Digital only
  Bound for Glory Show #: 576
- Rosalie Sorrels, May 4, 1986; tr-17863 (Box 2)
- Fred Small, November 9, 1986; tr-17864 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 592
- Bill Staines, April 10, 1988; tr-17865 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 638
- Stout, September 2, 1990; tr-17871 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 715
  Jerry Barrett collection
- Stout, September 2, 1990; tr-17912 (Box 2)
- Bob Franke, September 9, 1990; tr-17872 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 716
  Date on label is September 8, 1990
- Bob Franke, September 9, 1990; tr-17873 (Box 2)
- Tim Keller, September 30, 1990; tr-17874 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 719
- Kristina Olsen, October 14, 1990; tr-17875 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 720
- Peter Ostroushko and Dean McGraw, November 18, 1990; tr-17876 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 725
- Peter Ostroushko and Dean McGraw, November 18, 1990; tr-17914 (Box 2)
  Also labeled with dates March 21, 1999, April 3, 1999, and October 24, 1999
- Douglas and Willa Porter, October 6, 1991; tr-17881 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 753
- Douglas and Willa Porter, October 6, 1991; tr-17883 (Box 2)
  Also labeled with dates May 22, 1999 and August 8, 1999
- Dady Brothers, October 20, 1991; tr-17886 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 754
- Dady Brothers, October 20, 1991; tr-17887 (Box 2)
- Chuck Pyle, January 19, 1992; tr-17889 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 761
- Lou and Peter Berryman, April 12, 1992; tr-17890 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 771
- Lou and Peter Berryman, April 12, 1992; tr-17891 (Box 2)
- Woods Tea Company, April 26, 1992; tr-17892 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 773
  Date on label is April 25, 1992
- Woods Tea Company, April 26, 1992; tr-17893 (Box 2)
- Catie Curtis, May 3, 1992; tr-17894 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 774
- Dan Berggren and the Newton Street Irregulars, June 21, 1992; tr-17895 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 775
- McDonnell/Tane, July 5, 1992; tr-17896 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 777
- McDonnell/Tane, July 5, 1992; tr-17897 (Box 2)
- Mark Rust, September 26, 1993; tr-17900 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 818
  Date on label is September 30, 1993
- Mark Rust, September 26, 1993; tr-17901 (Box 2)
- Mark Rust, September 3, 1995; tr-17903 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 874
  Date on label is September 4, 1995
- Mark Rust, September 3, 1995; tr-17904 (Box 2)
- Chris Shaw, October 29, 1995; tr-17905 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 881
  Date on label is October 28, 1995
- Chris Shaw, October 29, 1995; tr-17906 (Box 2)
- Amy Gallatin, December 3, 1995; tr-17907 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 885
  Date on label is December 2, 1995. Also listed on label: Country Sampler; E Town Judy Collins
- John Kirk and Trish Miller, January 19, 1997; tr-17909 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 917
- Bill Staines, April 20, 1997; tr-17908 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 928
  Also labeled with date October 24, 1999
- Bill Staines, April 20, 1997; tr-17910 (Box 2)
- Garnet Rogers, May 3, 1998; tr-17911 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 964
  Also labeled with date October 28, 1990
- Simple Gifts, June 28, 1998; tr-17143 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 965
  Bound for Glory Tape #:
  Track:
- Ned Lucas with Joel T. Johnson, July 5, 1998; tr-17144 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 966
- Maria Sangiolo, July 12, 1998; tr-17145 (Box 1)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 967
- Mac Benford, Walt Koken, Bob Potts, February 21, 1999; tr-17913 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 989
  Also listed on label: 50s folk singer women
- Mark Rust, March 4, 2001; tr-17915 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 1058
  Also labeled with date April 24, 2000
- Bill Staines, April 8, 2001; tr-17916 (Box 2)
  Bound for Glory Show #: 1061
- Bill Staines, April 8, 2001; tr-17917 (Box 2)
- Encore Tapes
  - Bound For Glory - Encores I, Digital only
    Bound for Glory Show #: 375 - 394
  - Bound For Glory - Encores II, Digital only
    Bound for Glory Show #: 393 - 416
  - Encores Fall '80, Digital only
  - Bound For Glory - Son of Encore Tape (#393 09-Nov-1980 thru #416 09-Aug-1981), Digital only
  - Bound For Glory - Encore Tape Meets Godzilla (#418 13-Sep-1981 thru #425 08-Nov-1981), Digital only
    Bound for Glory Show #: 418 - 425